ID	Breed	Species Name	Origin	Average lifespan	Traits
A1	Dog	Poodle	Germany/France	10 - 18 years	Smart, agile, and easy to train. They are often chosen as family pets. They have thick, curly coats with dry hair, usually black, white, brown, gray or chestnut brown
A2	Dog	Pugs	China	14 - 15 years	Known for his adorable face and cheerful personality. This species has a wrinkled face, short snout, and curly tail. This dog breed has smooth, shiny fur that comes in many colors, but the most common are black and fawn. Their bodies are compact and square with well-developed muscles.
A3	Dog	Labrador Retriever	Older brother	10 - 12 years	Friendly, loyal, and intelligent. They work well as guard dogs and do rescue work. Strong body, broad head, brown eyes. Big ears, long tail. Their fur is almost straight, without any waves, and the common colors are black, yellow and chocolate.
A4	Dog	Siberian Husky	Russia	12 - 14 years	Strong body, upright ears, curly tail. Blue, gray, or brown eyes. The coat is thick, curly, and can be white, gray, black, red, and brown. They like to exercise and are not suitable for tropical environments.
A5	Dog	Shih Tzu	China	10 - 16 years	Small body, round head, large eyes. The tail is high and curved towards the back. The coat is long, smooth, naturally short and curly when a baby but will become longer and straighter as an adult, often styled in many colors such as white, yellow, monochromatic cream or mixed with brown, yellow or black.
A6	Dog	Dachshund	Virtue	12 - 16 years	They have long bodies, broad chests, sunken abdomens, active, solid bodies with very short limbs. They give this dog breed a unique and wise appearance. The head is elongated, the eyes are slightly bulging, the muzzle is long, with a strong jaw and extremely sharp teeth. Eyes are oval shaped, dark red or dark brown, very active and friendly. The ears are quite flexible and always hang loosely on either side of the cheeks. The hair of short-haired dogs is smooth, shiny and uniform, usually dark black, brown or gray with a light chestnut color.
A7	Dog	Chihuahua	Mexico	12 - 20 years	Chihuahu is small dog breed with a round head and short muzzle. It has large, round eyes, dark almost black, sometimes dark ruby red. The distinctive large ears are always kept pricked. The body is sturdy, longer than the height, the tail is curved over the back or crossed to one side. The short fur is sandy yellow, chestnut brown, silver, steel blue, light brown. They are courageous, extremely lively, proud and bold, they always express their affection and also require care from their owners.
A8	Dog	Golden Retriever	Older brother	10 - 12 years	Possesses a balanced and healthy body. They have plumage colors ranging from creamy yellow to golden brown (red is not recognized). The coat is made up of an outer waterproof layer and a thick layer of smooth hair inside. They have a large head, a slightly beveled snout but with a wide and very strong jaw and sharp teeth. The nose is black, the expressive eyes are brown with dark rims. The ears are medium-sized and drooping. The neck is long, strong and quite muscular. Wide chest. The tail is long and never curls. They are loyal, intelligent, and friendly. Suitable for families and can be used as a guard dog.
B1	Cat	Persian	Iran	12 - 16 years	Persian cats have round heads, short noses and large eyes. Concave ears and short tail. They have long, soft fur, and often require special hair care. They have a friendly, approachable and docile personality. Sociable with other animals, always likes peace. Persian cats also love children so they will not harm them.
B2	Cat	Siamese	Thailand	12 - 15 years	Siamese has a slim figure, tubular and slim body, little fat; slim legs; The tail is very slim and long, tapering towards the tip of the tail and the head is long, very pointed with extremely large ears. Dark blue eyes and long tail. Usually have short, smooth fur, often dark brown and white. They are very active cats, very curious about everything around them. Thai Siamese cats are very friendly, close and loyal to their owners. They always want to be with you, like to be petted and petted, and like to have you care and pay attention to them.
B3	Cat	Maine Coon	America	12 - 15 years	The Maine Coon cat's tail is quite long, tapered and has long, thick fur, looking like the tail of a North American raccoon. Their bodies are quite solid and muscular, necessary to support their large weight, and their chests are broad. They have thick and soft fur, often with long hair on the tail and ears and are brown in color
B4	Cat	Bengal	America	12 - 16 years	The cat's fur has striped patterns just like wild leopards. Cats have slim heads, large eyes, and are usually jade green and black. The cat's ears are large and erect, and the tail is small and elongated. Cats have long, muscular and healthy bodies. Bengal cats are intelligent, highly mobile, have quick reflexes and are full of energy. They are friendly, cheerful, affectionate, like to be close to humans, very obedient, easy to train, learn quickly and often like to be destructive at night.
B5	Cat	Ragdoll	America	12 - 17 years	Ragdoll cats have long fur and characteristic beautiful blue eyes. The round head is covered with shaggy fur, the muzzle is slightly long and pointed, and the thin ears are erect. Ragdolls often have main colors such as chocolate, lilac, cream, blue, etc. Ragdoll cats have a pleasant personality, docile but quite shy. They are gentle and gentle. Active, affectionate and very loyal, very suitable for homes with young children
B6	Cat	Sphynx	Canada	8 - 14 years	The Egyptian cat's body is smooth, hairless, and has pale skin. The whole body is covered with wrinkled skin. In fact, they still have a thin layer of fluff covering their entire body, making their body more sensitive than other cat breeds. Sphynx cats have two large ears. Although their skin color is not diverse, those with red or black striped skin will have great value. In contrast to his fierce, slightly scary appearance, he has an extremely adorable and cute personality. They are very friendly and active.
